b2s.com 2009-04-13

# b2s.com - Manufacturers, suppliers and products from Greater China

b2s.com respects its members' privacy seriously. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your product sourcing experience and to communicate with you about the most update product information. We do not sell, rent, give away, or loan any information regarding to its members to any third parties without the users' consent. This privacy policy covers b2s.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that b2s.com collects when users are on the b2s.com site and when using b2s.com's service. This policy also covers b2s.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that b2s.com's business partners share with b2s.com. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that b2s.com does not own or control, or to parties that b2s.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

b2s.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a b2s.com account, when you use certain b2s.com products or services, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. B2s.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. When you register with b2s.com, we ask for your name, email address, mailing address, phone, nature of business, and product interests. Once you register with b2s.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. b2s.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, b2s.com cookie information and the page you requested. b2s.com uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

b2s.com will not sell, rent, give away or loan any of your personally identifiable information to anyone. b2s.com will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of b2s.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the b2s.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guideline for specific products or services.

**Protection of children's privacy**

b2s.com are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we ill never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If b2s.com become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files. Please note: we may nevertheless maintain a record of that person's name and address in a "do not register" file to avoid subsequent registration by a child under the age of 13.

**Cookies**

b2s.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on you computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to b2s.com's cookies. b2s.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with b2s.com products and services. b2s.com gives you the ability to edit your B2s.com account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want B2s.com to contact you about specials and new products.

**Security**

Your b2s.com account information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

b2s.com may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback from or send an email to webmaster@b2s.com.

**Contact us**

**Address:** | Unit 101, 1/F., Stelux House, 698 Prince Edward Road East, San Po Kong, Kowloon, Hong Kong.  
---|---  
**Telephone:** | +852 2191 7808  
**Fax :** | +852 2191 7816  
**E-mail:** | [webmaster@b2s.com](mailto:webmaster@b2s.com)
